{"questions": [
    {"question": "Which of the following is NOT included in Generic Process Models?",
     "a":"Waterfall model",
     "b":"Evolutionary development",
     "c":"Formal systems development",
     "d":"Use-based development",
     "e":"None of the above",
     "correct": "4"},

     {"question": "Which of the following is NOT included in Specific Process Models?",
     "a":"Incremental model",
     "b":"Object-Based Development Model",
     "c":"Spiral Development Model",
     "d":"Package-Based Development Model",
     "e":"None of the above",
     "correct": "2"},

     {"question": "",
     "a":"Incremental model",
     "b":"Object-Based Development Model",
     "c":"Spiral Development Model",
     "d":"Package-Based Development Model",
     "e":"None of the above",
     "correct": "2"},

     {"question": "Which of the following is NOT included in Characteristics of Software?",
      "a":"Software does “wear out”.",
      "b":"Software is abstract and intangible.", 
      "c":"Software is abstract and intangible.",
      "d":"Most software is custom-built, rather than being assembled from existing components.",
      "e":"None of the above",
      "correct":"1"},

      {"question": "Which of the following is NOT included in Fundamental Process Activities of Software Process?",
       "a":"Specification",
       "b":"Development", 
       "c":"Validation",
       "d":"Evolution",
       "e":"None of the above",
       "correct":"5"},

      {"question": "Which of the following is NOT an advantage of the Waterfall Model?",
      "a":"Very clear from a managerial viewpoint - easy to model, plan, monitor, and understand",
      "b":"Many existing tools support this model", 
      "c":"Development is relatively slow and deliberate and thus, results in solid, well-constructed systems",
      "d":"Last explicit process model",
      "e":"None of the above",
      "correct":"4"},

      {"question": "Which of the following is NOT a description of the Waterfall model?",
      "a":"Linear sequential model",
      "b":"Describe a set of clear stages in the development process", 
      "c":"Based on engineering practice",
      "d":"Still used for large systems engineering projects",
      "e":"None of the above",
      "correct":"5"},

      {"question": "Which of the following is NOT a disadvantage of Evolutionary Development?",
      "a":"Cost, time, and resource estimation is difficult",
      "b":"Process is not visible", 
      "c":"Progress is difficult to measure",
      "d":"Less effective than waterfall model",
      "e":"None of the above",
      "correct":"4"},

      
      {"question": "Which of the following is NOT a description of the Incremental model?",
      "a":"Suggested by Mills 1980",
      "b":"In between waterfall and evolutionary", 
      "c":"Increase rework in the development process",
      "d":"Give customers opportunity to delay decisions",
      "e":"None of the above",
      "correct":"3"},

      {"question": "Which of the following is NOT an advantage of the Spiral Development Model?",
      "a":"delayed error elimination",
      "b":"Puts quality objectives up front", 
      "c":"Integrates development and maintenance",
      "d":"Provides a framework for simultaneous hardware/software development",
      "e":"None of the above",
      "correct":"1"},

      {"question": "Which of the following is NOT included in best practices for Rational Unified Process?",
      "a":"Develop software iteratively",
      "b":"Manage requirements", 
      "c":"Component based architecture",
      "d":"Visually model software",
      "e":"None of the above",
      "correct":"5"},

      {"question":"This is the discrepancy between an exact value and some approximation to it.",
      "a":"Round-off errors",
      "b":"Total numerical error",
      "c":"Truncation error",
      "d":"Approximation error",
      "e":"None of the above",
      "correct":"4"

      },

      {"question":"This is the summation of the truncation and round-off errors",
      "a":"Round-off errors",
      "b":"Total numerical error",
      "c":"Truncation error",
      "d":"Approximation error",
      "e":"None of the above",
      "correct":"2"

      },

      {"question":"_________ refers to how closely a computed or measured value agrees with the true value.",
      "a":"Precision",
      "b":"True value",
      "c":"Accuracy",
      "d":"Round-off errors",
      "e":"None of the above",
      "correct":""

      },

      {"question":"It is a special type of software that allows the user to enter and perform calculations on rows and columns of data.",
      "a":"Excel",
      "b":"Matlab",
      "c":"Mathcad",
      "d":"Gitlab",
      "e":"None of the above",
      "correct":"1"

      },

      {"question":"__________ helps you automate the builds, integration, and verification of your code.",
      "a":"Excel",
      "b":"Matlab",
      "c":"Mathcad",
      "d":"Gitlab",
      "e":"None of the above",
      "correct":"4"

      } 

      



      

]
}